Evgenii Grebenchuk *Frontend/React Developer*

058.561.2746 | gussmandva@gmail.com | LinkedIn | 24 y.o.

Tel-Aviv, Moshe Erem 8

Natural-born self-taught developer with vast experience in motion design and graphics. Jamstack enthusiast. Chosen as one of the 100 students for the Yandex Data Analysis Program and successfully finished the course. Strong background in cinema and photography. Experience as a filmmaker and as a programming tutor.

EDUCATION

Self-taught | 2021

Self taught: React. js, Redux, Sass, Framer-Motion, Styled-Components, advanced JavaScript and advanced CSS.

Data Analyst Program | Yandex100 | 2020-2021

Coursework Includes: Python, EDA, Data Collection and Storage (SQL), Automation, Making Data-Informed Business Decisions (Testing), Building Complex Projects

.NET Full Stack Developer | John Bryce | 2019-2020

Coursework Includes: OOP, AJAX, Angular 8, Web API, Entity Framework, ADO.NET

B.A. in Cinematography and Film/Video Production | Tel-Aviv University | 2019-2021

Achievements: Successfully selected as one of the 60 students in the directing department.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Expertise: JAVASCRIPT, HTML, CSS, Typescript, C#, Python, SQL

Frameworks: React, Vanilla JS, Angular

Skills: Redux, Axios, Sass, Styled Components, OOP, AJAX, Web API, Entity Framework, ADO.Net, Git,

Motion Graphic Design, Animation, Design, Color Grading, Photography, 3D animation

PROJECTS

Eugene Needs Work | Self-taught | 2021

My tech portfolio website l've created using React, Styled-Components, Lottie, Framer-motion.

My Photography/Videography site | Self-taught | 2021

Created a portfolio website using React, Framer motion. Tutorial-based.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Motion Graphics artist | Visualed | 2017-2017

 Worked on creating a digital branch of Bank Hapoalim. The animation I've created is still up to this date in all Hapoalim Digital branches.

<u>**Data Analyst Instructor**</u> | Yandex Practicum | October 2021-Present

- Gained crucial experience in being a tutor and explaining core programming concepts to students.

LANGUAGES

English | Fluent **Russian** | Native **Hebrew** | Fluent **German** | Intermediate